I was having a dream about that day in our second year of high school.
The incredible day that brought us together.
Please make yourself comfortable, sir.
I'll come back to get you once the bride is ready.
It shouldn't be too much longer now.
Excuse me. Do you know if the bride's sisters have arrived?
Yes. They came quite early, so they've been here a while.
Oh. Right, thanks.
Pardon me, sir. The bride is calling for you.
What's up?
Almost done getting changed. Wait there a sec.
By the way, I heard that the girls are here.
Who knows what they've got planned.
I swear, those four haven't changed since high school.
Still nothing but trouble.
I had that same dream again.
How many times am I going to revisit that day?
It's been permanently etched into my mind.
And it was a total nightmare.
We're ready!
Thought I'd woken up, but looks like I'm still dreaming.
Well, what can you do?
I like it.
Oh
We win again thanks to the five of you ladies yotsuba in particular well done
You've improved drastically
You think so? I'm not sure
Yeah, we're all quintuplets so we're the same right?
Nope sorry I know what I saw the rest of you oughta learn from yotsuba here she's clearly been practicing hard
Learn from me? Wow
We should head down to the shop now that the match is over it'll be closing soon
Have a little shopping trip planned?
Yeah, we're gonna pick out a special present for our mom to celebrate her getting better
We've all been saving up to buy her a pretty bouquet
All right time to go get some flowers
Geez you're always so pushy Ichika
Well come on you guys
Yay!
We've gotta pick the most perfect ones
What kind do you think she'd like most?
I heard somewhere that you're supposed to get carnations if they're for your mother
Carnations huh? That's weird
Yeah I don't get it but I've heard the same thing before
Yotsuba how much do we have again?
Let me check
I think I dropped our wallet
Huh?
Any luck over there?
No there's still no sign of it
He had it before the match started so it has to be around here somewhere
I'll go look where we were earlier
Yotsuba
But
He lost it
And it's all my fault
What do I do?
I'm sorry everyone
I really messed up
Don't be so hard on yourself
I'm sure that any one of us could've lost it just as easily
Yeah
When we mess up it's on all five of us together
Thank you guys
I know it's not what we were planning on but
While looking for the wallet I found some pretty flowers
Do you think
These might work?
Oh yeah?
Wild flowers?
Sorry
I shouldn't try to act like I can fix it
We found the same ones that you did
All four of us
They really are quintuplets
Hey I'm home
Are you girls asleep already?
We're so glad you're better Mom
We got these to celebrate
Here you go
We gathered them for you ourselves
That's right
Thanks for working so hard
Thanks for everything
Oh she's just standing there
Maybe this isn't good enough
It's a wonderful gift
But the best present of all is knowing that the five of you are healthy
And happy
Thank you
My sweet girls
I'd say we're all done here
Let's head home
Do you think Dad was the one who left that bouquet?
Not a chance
Can't believe the last summer break of our high school career is almost over
And it'll be full speed ahead on festival prep once the second term starts up
You're going to be taking some time off of school aren't you Ichika?
Have to since I've got that movie to shoot
Will you have enough attendance days to graduate?
Yeah I'll be okay
Butero says that he'll be giving me some one-on-one tutoring too
Seriously though
I can't believe we're back here again
Kicked out after just six months on our own
Pretty awful luck
Everything's still clean
I wonder if it was Epita
He must have been keeping it up while we were gone
Man, I forgot how big it was
Thanks a lot
I appreciate it
Huh?
Itsuki?
What were you up to in the staff office?
I just had a few questions about the lecture today
So I stopped by
Gotcha
I was asking about the lecture
How could you do it?
What if it was Epita?
He must have been keeping it up while we were gone
Man, I forgot how big it was
Thanks a lot
I appreciate it
Huh?
Itsuki!
What were you up to in the staff office?
I just had a few questions about the lecture today
So I stopped by
Gotcha
I was asking about the festival
They want the class reps to take charge of everything
Do they?
Speaking of class reps
Yeah
I don't know if this kind of festival is really Iwasugi's thing
Anyway
Apparently it's tradition for the third years to do food stalls
Karage and frankfurters
Buttered potatoes are nice too
I'm sorry
I have to help out with cram school
But let's talk more about this later, okay?
I thought Itsuki would be at least a little interested
Has everyone left already?
Need something, Yotsuba?
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt you
It's just
The food stalls for the festival, right?
Just give me a second, okay?
I have no time to waste right now
Uh, sure
Sure
What's
Rai-ha was telling me about that commercial Ichka was in.
Just wait. I'll make it a summer you'll never forget.
She's doing well as an actress now. Getting out there, realizing her dream.
And Ichka's working toward becoming a teacher.
She's not cut out for it, but that's her dream.
So, Yotsuba.
Yes?
Have you given any thought to what your future will hold?
Wow, that came out of nowhere.
I've never really considered it.
Well, you have a great deal of talent when it comes to athletics.
I'm sure there'll be options for you in that field.
I'm ready now.
Let's go gather some intel on last year's food stalls.
Are you sure? I mean what you said before about not having any time.
No time to waste. It's our last big school event. I have to make it count.
If I'm going to do this, I want to have fun in the process.
Time's a finite thing. There's never enough of it.
So I'll need your help.
Okay! I've got your back!
These are the food stall items that were popular last year.
If there's something you'd like to do that's not on this list, go ahead and shout it out!
My vote is for takoyaki. I don't see any reason to stray away from what works. And besides, you did the research for that list, didn't you?
Nice! This'll give me the chance to show off my takoyaki skills from work.
Yes, sounds good to me as well.
Dunno. What do you think?
So, any other suggestions?
I want to do taiyaki!
Bubble tea!
Miku, what would you like to do?
Pancakes, maybe?
Well, um, there isn't any sales data on record through last year.
It could work, though.
Good suggestion. Thanks.
Yeah, thanks, Miku.
I was thinking that would be good, too. You might look so cute!
Let's leave it here for today. We'll decide another time.
Nakano, this concert sounds cool. Do you think maybe we could be part of it?
Yeah, of course!
The Clothing Club's going to be presenting these. We might not get any visitors, though.
Oh! That's beautiful!
We could put posters up in the designated areas. I'm happy to help you out if you'd like me to.
Thank you so much!
Yotsuba's so popular.
Why is no one asking for my advice?
We lose.
Are there invitations that we can send out to family?
Absolutely!
Invitations...
I'm on board with the food stall idea.
Whatever we go with, it's going to be fun to make.
Yeah, I can't wait to start.
You're going to be on the cooking team?
We're going to have outside customers, you know.
You could end up poisoning the entire neighborhood if you're not careful.
I've gotten better, thank you very much.
Besides, I have you.
So I'm not worried.
I'm not worried.
Well, obviously.
If I'm around to supervise, everything will go exactly the way it's supposed to.
Thanks for waiting!
You've been busy.
Think maybe you're working too hard?
It's our last big school event, right?
I want to make sure we finish the festival without any regrets.
The last one.
Yeah.
I appreciate this.
I'm sure you've got plenty to do without having to help me study, too.
Do you have enough time for your college prep?
Seems like the festival is keeping you pretty busy.
Actually, I just got my evaluation back from my preferred school.
Really?
It's for my eyes only!
Nobody can look at it but me!
Okay, let me guess.
You got an A.
Well, that's no fun.
Of course you did well.
But that's because you're naturally studious.
It's a lot harder for mere mortals like us.
So please keep looking out for everyone.
We're not at the finish line yet.
You don't need to worry.
Everything's going to turn out exactly as it should.
I swear, Ichka.
I'll make this the best school festival ever.
Just admit that you're wrong, boys.
You're the ones who have it wrong.
I bet you couldn't find anyone who doesn't love a fluffy pancake.
Pack us up on this, Miku.
Oh, well, uh...
You saw the data from last year.
There's not a single human in this country who hates takoyaki.
Right, Nino?
Yeah.
You said yourself that you like pancakes, Nino.
So why are you siding with them?
You didn't really mean it, right?
You didn't really mean it.
Okay, here's how it is, people.
I was the one who proposed takoyaki.
I'll take responsibility.
Also, cooking and eating are two different things.
Sure, pancakes are awesome, but they're tricky enough to make that even I screw them up sometimes.
Arguing about it's not gonna get us anywhere.
We should just do both.
I didn't expect people to be at each other's throats like that.
Seriously!
And why'd you even bring up pancakes?
Futaro said his mom would bake bread for him every day back when he was little.
That made me think about our family and the traditions we had.
Yeah, that's fair, I guess.
Those were pretty memorable and super fluffy.
But they're also not the kind of thing you can learn to pull off overnight.
So you've really made them before?
It was the first dish I ever tried to cook.
Takoyaki is the easier way to go, for sure.
It's definitely for the best.
Okay, but still.
Did you have to be so blunt about it?
You know me.
I prefer a direct approach.
Nino, Miku.
Didn't expect to find you together.
Futaro, you need something?
Never mind, it's not important.
I mean, I know we're all really busy, but let's enjoy the festival!
Talk to you guys later!
Kay, that was weird.
Actually, I need to talk to him for a second. I'll see you at home.
Miku! Futaro!
Yeah, what's up, Miku?
There's something I want to tell you before the festival starts.
You know, there's something that I wanted to tell you, too.
In that case, do you think you could tell me yours first?
Sure. Your evaluation!
I heard that you got an A!
I want to congratulate you. I know it wasn't easy.
Mm-mm.
Yes, it's been a long road for all of us.
But if we manage to get you into a university, it will have been worth every grueling second!
It's gratifying when your hard work pays off, isn't it?
Um, yeah, I guess.
Anyway, Futaro.
Go out with me.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean that in a weird way or anything.
I was just hoping that maybe we could go somewhere this Sunday.
Uh?
Oh, hey! Are you leaving for the day, too?
Yeah, I am. I was looking for someone to walk home with me.
Oh, I'm sorry, then. But you'll have to keep looking.
I'm going straight to cram school from here, so I'm afraid I can't help.
How very studious of you.
I, uh, was wondering. How did your entrance evaluation go?
Not as badly as I expected it to. I think I snagged a bee.
Uh?
Whoa! What's wrong?
I don't know what to do, Nino! I've been putting in the hours studying so much!
And the plan got me! My future's as bleak as ever!
I'm a pathetic shadow of our mother!
I might as well give up my dream of becoming a teacher right now!
It's over!
Hey, uh, it'll be alright.
I'm sorry for losing my composure.
The advice my teacher gave me was to discuss the issue with my parents.
But it's not that simple.
Yeah, he probably wouldn't want to bother, would he?
No! I didn't mean it like that.
I just don't want to give Dad anything else to worry about.
Huh? Him worry? He would have to care first.
You have to admit we've had a privileged life.
And that's because of him, though it did take me a long time to realize it too.
Those flowers were definitely from him.
He hasn't involved himself in our lives directly much over the years.
But I think he always worried about us from a distance.
I'm not buying it.
Well, I should get going.
I'll talk to Shimura, the teacher who's been helping me out at the cram school.
There's supposed to be a special class taught by a famous instructor coming up.
So maybe I can look into attending that.
Nino!
I got the festival invitation that you were asking me about.
I'm gonna pass, actually.
Are you sure?
It was a momentary lapse of judgment to consider inviting Dad.
I don't know. I thought it was a good idea.
It's not like he'd come, you know.
He rarely even shows up at home, just lurks in the shadows being all silent and judgy.
That's a bit harsh.
I mean...
It's the girls who were staring me down before.
I'd rather not deal with them right now. Let's go another way.
So let me make sure I have this straight.
In a nutshell, you're suspicious of Nino's motives for siding with the boys.
You think she's doing it because she's hoping to get closer to one of them for whom she harbors secret feelings.
Exactly! And if Yusuke is the guy she's after, then we can all guess how that'll turn out.
I wouldn't stand a chance against her.
Sakura, you don't know that for sure.
You're mistaken.
She's not interested in a member of the Takoyaki group.
I'm certain of that much at least.
So you can relax.
I don't believe you.
How would you know whether she's interested in somebody?
The class rep is supposed to be a neutral party who doesn't take sides in any disputes that may occur.
Huh? What are you saying? That has nothing to do with it.
Yeah, seriously.
The thing is that Nino...
She likes me!
So please, take it easy on her.
Wow. Sorry, Uesugi. But you should stop fantasizing.
It wouldn't be very nice to spread that about Nino.
But no! It's true!
Maybe lurking in the shadows isn't always a bad thing.
I'm sure that Dad has his reasons too.
I don't remember giving you permission to enter my office.
Leave immediately, Uesugi.
Come on! At least find out why I'm here before saying that.
I've got some interesting info for you.
Seems like he's come back. For the first time in over a decade.
Right here we have Ann. And if you look behind her, you'll see San.
All right, now here's a question for you. Who out there can tell me what this one's name was again?
I don't remember giving you permission to enter my office.
Leave immediately, Uesugi.
Come on! At least find out why I'm here before saying that.
I've got some interesting info for you.
I don't remember. First of all, we get your humans right there!
Failure and位置 matters for me even more or less.
Okay. I'm Ready for you, Ira.
I'm saw your hands.
You've walked up to see Ibiza.
Oh, man!
I'm very mercønive!
We don't know!
Let me google the best decision to turn on to my Spinjolak!
But we're gonna tell him I don't do this!
Do you have the best videos for you?
I do have some great videos for you.
Seems like he's come back.
For the first time in over a decade.
They look alike. These five little penguins actually happen to be sisters
Sounds familiar
That one does kind of remind me of Nino
So is that one you then?
You're not funny, you know
Futuro? Truth is, I want to study cooking
And that means I won't be going to college
I'm sorry to disappoint you
I see
Well, if that's your decision, you have my support
That's not a real supportive face
I mean, going to technical school was always an option
It's not like it's a bad one
I don't think going to a university is a bad option either
And maybe I'm making the wrong call
Even so, I'd like to start working toward my dream when I graduate
That's what I wanted to tell you
Because you've become somebody who's very special to me, Futuro
You mean that in a...
A weird way?
Of course I do
Where was Miku going with that old discussion?
She's clearly talking about more than just her career plans
Well, I've told you mine now
I guess that makes it your turn again
Is there something else I need to tell her?
Welcome home, big bro
What are you doing here, Itsuki?
I brought you this
From Yotsuba
She says she forgot to give it to you
Oh, great
Thanks
Alrighty
The curry's ready if you guys are
I'll take some, thank you
Are you sure you have time to be doing this?
I heard about your evaluation
That doesn't mean I'm giving up my choice of schools
I'll skip the festival to study if that's what it takes
Please, I just need you to get in somewhere
Everything I've done to help you all these months will be for nothing if that doesn't happen
You don't really believe that
Ichika's working as an actress
Miku wants to be a chef
Is it enough?
Has the time you spent with them been for nothing?
No
I'd like to think it hasn't
As invested as you may be in our education
We're more than just students and their tutor
And we have been for a while now
Wasuki
Whatever happens
Even if there's failure in our future
I can promise you this much at least
You won't regret being our tutor
Or meeting the five of us
Our time together has been a lot of things
But never pointless
Miku's right
It's my turn
Attention everyone
Please gather in the gymnasium
We will now begin the opening ceremony for the 29th Asahi High School Hinodei Festival
First, sit back and enjoy this opening act performed by our very own girl group
Love Vacation
There's no turning back now
Nobody will stand in our way
You are only mine
So I'll set up a big heat outline here
Yeah, yeah
Love Vacation
Chills
Can't stop my feelings
There's no...
He knows doing great!
I'm surprised you volunteered
Try to push away
But I will never stop
On this Love Vacation
The 2019 O'Day Festival is now in session
Have fun!
You're so good at this!
Who taught you how to make them?
I learned at work
We've got customers
Thank you for stopping by!
I hope it settles down a little by 3
Done!
I think that's it for the inspection
Wait!
Yotsuba!
Hey look!
It's red!
I'm sorry!
You're so good at this!
Who taught you how to make them?
I learned at work
We've got customers
Thank you for stopping by!
I hope it settles down a little by 3
Done!
I think that's it for the inspection
I hope it settles down a little by three.
Done.
I think that's it for the inspection.
Wait, Yotsuba!
Hey, look! It's red!
Great job on the opener.
You were super cute up there.
Please take one of our corn dogs, free of charge.
Thank you.
With all those people swamping me,
I couldn't even check out the food stalls.
I wonder if this is what it's always like for Ichika.
Nina!
Geez, way to give me a heart attack.
I enjoyed the opening number you guys did.
It was a perfect way to kick off the festival.
Please don't tell me this is how you're planning to spend the rest of it.
I should be able to get it done by three.
Don't worry.
I'm exhausted.
Any idea what Fu's been up to?
This is the building you want.
Thank you for bringing me here.
You seem like a very considerate young man.
Uwasugi!
We want to turn this into a rest area.
Think you can help?
Uh, sure.
Hey, I'm here.
Miku!
Glad you made it.
You're late.
Where have you been?
Never mind that.
We're all here now, aren't we?
Nope.
Still one to go.
Hey, Ichika.
Wow, you came!
And you didn't bother giving us a heads up?
Surprised you weren't mobbed by fans.
I managed somehow.
Now we're all present and accounted for.
Hands down, my favorite group of people.
I agree.
Wow, look at that spread.
We bought all kinds of food from the stalls.
Finally!
I've been waiting for this all day.
I love you, all five of you.
Well, that was unexpected.
Yeah.
And what does it even mean?
I wish things were simpler,
and the six of us could always be together like this,
but we can't.
Life's not simple, and I have to give an answer.
Futuro, it's okay.
Thank you.
Of course, I'm not such an idiot
that I would do it in the middle of a festival.
And to be honest, I don't quite know myself yet.
Please, give me until the last day.
Are you kidding with this?
That's so anticlimactic.
Let's get back to it, then, starting with a toast.
I want orange juice.
Where's the matcha soda?
There isn't any.
Here we are.
You've almost got it figured out.
This has been a long road.
Not like solving a math problem, is it?
You're teasing me now?
I have to admit, I am envious.
Here, you need a drink, too.
Oh, thank you.
Well, then, I propose a toast
to the first day of the festival.
Cheers, everyone.
Welcome all to day two of the Hinodei Festival.
We'll be covering the action throughout the day,
but first off, let's interview a few of the...
Nakano, are you here?
You do remember me from track, don't you?
Let's meet a...
You're still running, right?
Hey, that's my microphone.
I'm sorry.
I should be going.
Come on.
Okay, let's try again.
Oh, hello there, ma'am.
What brings you to the festival grounds?
Oh, not much.
I'm here to see a childhood friend.
There's no work for you today, Uesugi.
Huh?
You should have fun.
Go enjoy the festival.
You've earned it.
How can I enjoy it?
I didn't even bring money for food.
Oh, I know somewhere I can go.
There you are.
Hutano, you've grown up a lot.
Takebayashi!
Wow, you're terrible at this game.
Try aiming it further to the right.
I'm just missing because you're bugging me.
Oh, hey, do you see that one back there?
Win it for me, would you?
So after all those nice things Futuro said yesterday,
he's out on a date with another girl.
Looks that way.
Uesugi's a popular guy, I guess.
Futuro, over here.
Okay, okay.
Fresh pancakes, nice and hot.
Look, Futuro.
They're selling pancakes.
Let's get some.
Oh, yeah.
The girls in my class are running this one.
Who's that?
I appreciate you girls for taking care of my Futuro.
Hold on, Mai.
I don't believe we've met.
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Takebayashi.
Futuro and I were in the same class in elementary school.
Is that so?
Well, he happens to be in the same high school class as me and all my sisters.
Though I think we're too involved in his life to refer to ourselves as just classmates.
Wow, what a wonderful coincidence.
Would you believe I used to help Futuro with schoolwork too?
He was always such a troublemaker, so I was pretty shocked when he asked me to tutor him.
No, no.
I'm the one doing the tutoring.
Oh, I understand.
Well, that explains everything then.
So out of all of us, now we know who's closest to him.
Yotspa, this is too much.
I...
Uasuki means more to me than you could...
That's very sweet of you.
If you taught him a long time ago, then I guess you could say that we're sort of indebted to you in a roundabout way.
Technically, you're the person who spent the most time around Uasuki.
Although, the quality of the time spent is what really matters.
Come on. You guys are starting to embarrass me.
Ease up, Takebayashi. Stop messing with them.
I don't have many friends, and all of these girls mean a lot to me.
You've grown up a lot, haven't you?
I'm sorry, you two.
Could I order one pancake, please?
Um, it's dripping.
Yotspa?
I'm fine. Sorry, I should get back to work.
Look, Fu.
I want you to know that my feelings about you haven't changed.
You're back. Good talk?
Yeah. I think Futado's doing well.
And the quintuplets are great girls, too.
Huh? Quintuplets?
Give it your best, Futado.
Was this the right choice?
Or was it wrong to even make a choice like this in the first place?
Three days was nowhere near enough time to figure that out.
Sadly, three days was all I had.
This concludes the Asahi High School Festival.
The after party, and all of our scheduled programming.
The taxi's running late.
Hey, Futado.
By the way, I heard Ichika Nakano goes to this high school, too.
Oh, man, I love her.
She was really gorgeous in that drama.
Ooh!
I'd love to do a kissing scene like that if it was with her.
Hmm.
Are you disappointed to hear I did a kissing scene?
No.
I'm an actress.
It's part of the job sometimes.
That's not the point.
I guess not, since you've already had your first kiss anyway.
Wait!
How did you know that?
It was an accident.
Oh, so you actually have.
Uh...
All right, who'd you kiss?
Um, I still don't know.
All five of you were dressed like Ichiki that day.
Hmm.
Well, who'd you think it was?
Uh...
The taxi's here.
You lucked out this time.
Hey, there's a chance I won't be able to go to the school festival.
So, could I ask you for your answer now?
Hmm?
Um, but it's okay if you haven't decided yet.
Listen.
I choose none of you.
That's my answer.
How dare you!
Get yourself together or you'll be sorry!
Sorry!
And cut!
Great job!
Exactly what I wanted!
Um, I hope you're not hurt.
Is it me?
Or are you used to this?
Ah...
Another good day of work.
Time to go relax at the hotel.
Ichika, there you are!
Is something wrong?
I just got a phone call.
They said that your sister collapsed.
Ah!
Seems like you're feeling a bit better.
Take it easy, okay?
Uh...
Nino!
Futaro!
Didn't think you were coming.
Yeah.
I called, but I couldn't stop worrying till I came by.
How's everyone else?
Not bad.
They're getting settled in right now.
But don't worry about us.
I promise we'll be okay.
All right, then.
That's good.
I need to head back to the campus to do some more cleaning.
You guys might as well walk each other home, right?
Uh, okay.
Well then, guess I'll call it a day now.
Actually, hold on.
Are you done with everything, too?
Yeah.
Great!
Then we should go for a walk.
This place is pretty spread out, huh?
Remember last time we came here?
Yeah, for the fireworks festival.
It feels a little empty without the booths and people around.
It's not completely deserted, though.
Mm-hmm.
You know, it's pretty common for couples to start dating at this festival.
Especially during the big after-party when the third day's over.
I figured maybe you knew that, and that was why you said what you did.
Heh.
You've known me way too long to think I'm the type who keeps up with stuff like that.
Oh, come on now.
Sometimes you do stoop to the level of us regular people.
Huh?
How so?
I've seen you peek inside expensive cars.
You get crazy excited when you go on vacation.
You like to shout from the top of a mountain.
You noticed all that?
Uh-huh.
Just a few of the things that make you so cute.
You should value those sincere feelings more.
Huh?
So please, stop saying that you aren't choosing anyone.
But I still don't know for sure how I feel.
Either you're overthinking all of this, or you're just avoiding thinking about it.
Remember our talk about kissing?
Out of Nino, Miku, Yotsuba, and Itsuki.
Be honest.
Who would you have been the happiest to find out it was?
Just kidding.
Oh, a fending machine.
Go get yourself something.
It's my treat.
Pick whatever drink sounds good to you.
What?
I'll be waiting on the bench.
What are you doing?
By the way!
Black tea's Nino, green's Miku, juice's Yotsuba, and canned coffee is Itsuki.
Uh-that's not fair.
I had to do something.
What's it going to be?
Futaro.
That was rude of me.
I kept her waiting for too long.
She and I have always communicated this way.
We're both the oldest child.
I know how rough that can be.
You were looking at my lips, weren't you?
Oh, you woke up.
Why were you watching?
It's just, I still don't know which one of you I kissed that day.
It could have been you.
Oh.
Man, I'm creepy.
Kinda.
Well then, was it me?
Oh, Ichika!
Wouldn't it be easier to figure it out by kissing each girl instead of looking?
Uh, maybe, but is that what you did it for?
I guess you're used to it from acting, though.
Oh, that drama I told you about yesterday?
It was with another actress.
What?
But kissing a guy on set?
I don't think I'm ready for that.
What I'm saying is, you were my first.
Not everyone gets to share a kiss with a classmate in high school.
So don't ever forget it.
Oh, I should have asked you.
Did you like it?
You don't have to be condescending.
Value your sincere feelings, I said.
Aw, you're being shy.
It's time I started taking my own advice.
It doesn't matter who Fudero chooses.
Because I know my feelings aren't going away anytime soon.
This concludes the Asahi High School Festival, the after-party, and all of our scheduled programming.
Well then, I propose a toast.
To the first day of the festival.
Cheers, everyone!
This is a ridiculous amount of fun.
But I'm complaining, don't talk about any other spell.
Mino?
Aren't you going to change out of that flashy costume?
Yeah.
I just wanted you to see it first.
Mm-mm.
Mino was cute out there, huh?
I guess.
I was supposed to be a part of the opening ceremony, but luckily she took over for me.
And she did a great job of it.
You need to learn to stop saying yes to everyone who asks for something.
I heard that you've been helping the drama club, too.
At some point, you're going to burn out, you know.
You're always so protective of your sisters.
Hey, that's not the only reason I did it.
I needed to find out if Dad was here.
And I figured if I could look out over the whole audience, then maybe I would see him.
Your dad's coming?
Maybe.
We wanted him to, so we sent an invitation.
But I didn't see any sign of him.
Well, no surprise there.
It doesn't bother me.
I see.
There's still a chance he got here late, though.
Do you want to go look around?
Damn, he's not here.
Have you heard from him?
Not yet.
What's with you?
How can you keep walking around with me after that big confession, like nothing happened?
I'm going to call him.
Hey, don't do that.
It's okay.
I wasn't expecting him to come anyway.
You had to work up a lot of courage to send that invitation.
You sure you don't mind?
I'm going to believe in him.
Come over and try some nice, fluffy pancakes!
They're right over here!
It's kind of surprising.
The pancake shop's getting more business than yesterday.
Yeah, people are starting to hear some positive buzz about us.
Nino, Uesugi said you're serving pancakes.
I hope this is the right place.
I'm starving.
How's it going?
Hello there, boss.
Just who I wanted to see.
I can't tell if she's being sarcastic.
Wow, I thought that was Dad for a second.
Thank you for joining us at the Asahi High School Festival.
Day two has officially come to an end.
Have a great evening.
I feel like we've got a pretty good shot at being the top seller.
I'm tired of waiting.
Here, time to go.
Uesugi, do what you want, but I'm done.
Huh?
I sent him an invite, and he never showed up.
He clearly doesn't care about us, and he never did.
There's one more day of the festival that I don't even care,
because if it doesn't work out, I'll regret hoping for it at all.
Listen, Nino, I don't know much about your family's past,
except the fact that you have a strained relationship with your father.
But there's something you're not seeing.
He looks at me with these suspicious eyes.
The eyes of a father protecting his daughter.
Why would he be that way with me if he didn't care about me?
That's why I always complain.
Because you guys are a pain in the ass.
Hey, Uesugi!
Is this the guy you're looking for?
I was looking through the footage,
and I found someone who matches your description exactly!
So where did you come from today, sir?
Uh, I'm getting a call from work.
I'm sorry, I should be going.
Oh, come on!
What do you think? Is that the guy?
Yeah, thanks.
It looks like he was here after all.
Should we go?
Okay.
Take me to Dad right now.
Silly me.
Why did I chicken out like that?
Even when I fail, I keep on trying.
Because that's the kind of person I am.
I don't know.
Hm?
Hello.
I've come here to return your daughter to you, sir.
What happened today?
I'd like you to leave before it gets dark out.
In a minute.
It's almost done.
You should have some.
I know you were at the festival.
Pancakes?
they're not expensive to make and the girls always appreciate them i wanted to make one
last batch don't be silly you'll get to make them again soon nakano i can't thank you enough for
everything you've done that being said i want you to stop this don't waste your time on me when mine
is running out i'd really prefer you didn't talk about running out of time like that i refuse to
say goodbye to my precious teacher your teacher huh that was so many years ago now besides if you
left the girls behind you know they'd be terribly lonely yes you're right
leaving them is my greatest regret i was supposed to be here to see them grow up
but they're still so young i'm indebted to you nakano but i do have one more favor to ask of you
once i'm discharged let me make you some pancakes will you i think that you would really enjoy them
miku was the one who made the batter she was an awful cook at first but now she's got a goal
and she's working toward it and it's not just her over the past few years the five of us have grown
up in a lot of ways and will keep growing so i want you there to see it okay dad
he ate it but i can't read his expression is he happy or disgusted
this flavor i get the sense you wanted to be direct huh direct you made quite a few of these
it'd be impossible to finish them myself next time we'll all eat them together
that was weird um anyway yeah that sounds really nice good for you nino i'm gonna use the restroom
wait a minute there uasugi was this something that you planned no sir yes it was he's the one
who brought me to see you well as their tutor that's not part of your job description
and again it was something i wasn't able to do myself so i suppose it's a good thing i hired you
after all i may not be the best father but i do suggest that you take great care in your
relationship with my daughter's uasugi hey fu thank you for today and for everything else
um about tomorrow there's something i wanted to uh careful
that was close
what are you two doing oh crap nothing dino just tripped i'm leaving now just great
right goodbye then well that was terrifying you didn't get hurt did you
when you're in love you have to be assertive
what did you say hey dad i want to tell you something
no matter how much my relationship with my sisters may change my feelings for him aren't
going anywhere it's been amazing having fu as a tutor so thank you
this concludes the asahi high school festival the after party and all of our scheduled programming
hey doesn't he go to our school looks like an enemy spy just what i'd expect from those jerks
we have to beat their dumb takoyaki come on let's fight
uh look actually there's something i wanted to say to you about that
we need to stop competing and get along the festival would be much more fun that way
or that's what i would say if i had the guts can't find him okay i'll go check over this
way
hey uesugi can you walk over to the takoyaki stall and tell those idiots to stop spying on
us just bury the hatchet already would you um i know why don't i try spying on them i mean
assuming that no one has a problem with that all right guys we'll defeat the girls tomorrow
yeah what do we do now futaro if someone can fix this it's you i know it i mean you're from
the opposite side but that might be exactly what it takes to change their minds at least that's my
gut feeling whether you believe it or not is up to you though
right then i choose to believe it
um hello there what the heck nakano what's the head of team pancake want here
if you don't mind i'd like to buy one order please
huh
these look great thank you so much be careful they're super hot
i will
i'd love for the girls in our class to have some of this
huh
after they're done for the day i'll bring them here to try it
that way they'll be able to see firsthand that you guys are doing your best
i'm i'm not sure how i feel about that yeah they said that takoyaki was lame remember
i don't want to make them any all right that's enough
futaro just wait i can do this i'll speak my mind
i'm sorry for not saying anything before today but i'm sure you guys don't want it to end like
this either so let's stop arguing the school festival is for all of us
it's about having fun together let's make it one we can be proud of
yeah maida i did see you giving an order of takoyaki to matsui
dude i said not to mention that
got some explaining to do
how could you betray us like that
that means i could have brought an order to marayama
i'd give yuri some damn it there's a certain someone that i wanted to make an order for too
okay can you help us then for their sake
yeah gladly thanks futaro you're the one who made that happen
i didn't do anything you inspired them to change their ways
you're stronger now miku
this accident is unfortunate but we have no choice but to close down class 3-1's takoyaki stand
miku i found her with zugi he was outside oh and he's talking to some girl
do you know her no you don't think you remember what he said yesterday
um you know about how he loved all of us we should just believe in that
oh i will when i first met him he told me that it was important for me to believe in the things i
care about i've never forgotten that and when i think about what i care about most it's always
been futaro i've only gotten this far because i loved him and believed in him
uh miku
long day no see it's too bad about the stall huh
futaro come with me the rooftop i thought we weren't allowed up here during the festival
it's fine i think this is a safe place to talk
bullshit you're enjoying the fact that we had to close up shop i know you are
no one said we were enjoying it you're just mad because you caused a fire with your stupidity
shut up no you you brought those two up to the roof
well at least they can't cause any more trouble this way
they won't i'm the one who's going to cause trouble
huh nakano
miku would you please explain this letter
you two you have to get along the guys and girls are both being stubborn about this
we're high school students next year we'll be in college so aren't you embarrassed to be
bickering like children pancakes and takoyaki are equally good things just like guys and
girls are we've all worked hard to make this festival a success
why can't either of you see that it's been uncomfortable between us ever since we started
prepping it's supposed to be fun i've refrained from saying that but i can't anymore
miku easy the girls are exhausted from working so hard all day
there's no reason the guys can't go lend them a hand at the pancake stall
huh i don't know even if i'm okay with doing that everyone else might not be
don't worry i can make them understand leave everything to me
sorry i'd kind of given up i figured the best we could do was draw a line in the sand
you really taught me a lesson
miku
who's that girl tell me what girl back at the shooting game
oh we were friends as kids do you like her
like in that way uh she's just a friend
oh good i'm relieved i've been resisting the urge to ask you
you have really you don't need to hold back for my sake you know
in that case i want to kiss you
i know i told you not to hold back but how do we end up here
i guess i can ask you for your answer again later
no matter how high a wall stands in my way
as long as i believe in myself i know i can cross over it
this concludes the asahi high school festival the after party and all of our scheduled programming
thanks i hope you enjoy
oh no queen emerald
it's over for you heroes
though i would prefer not to slay you where you stand
so i order you to join my forces
i was so worried it wouldn't work out
i can't thank you enough for covering the role for me nakano
sure anytime always happy to make myself useful
i'm here to perform the safety inspection
oh yeah thanks
looks like their ingredients meet the expectations
you should clean up those paper scraps in case they catch fire
at this rate i think i'll be done by 3 p.m
step right up
thanks for helping us advertise
here i want to give you a coupon
i can't wait to try it
so tired
you did a great job today
you're not built for all this physical labor
you should go take a break
i'm fine but thanks anyway
can i get through i'm trying to finish this by 3
i'm worried about you
i'm not letting you go until you listen to me
right i guess i haven't eaten since this morning
with all these food options around
well at least it's an easy fix
go get some karaage and regain your strength
you're sure you don't want this
uh-huh i'm totally full so i don't need it
that was just because i'm still digesting
now let's get these moved
yotsuba thank you for this
i'm lucky that you're around
oh come on don't make it a big deal
we help each other out all the time don't we
to be honest
no matter how tough things get
it was suki's approval makes it all worth it
two more days till he answers us
after that we probably won't have to carry on like this anymore
but if he ends up choosing me then
damn it it's not fair we've all worked so hard
and now we have to close up shop on day two
i mean they did warn us that it would be dangerous
after an incident like that there really isn't anything else we can do
shit
can i work here
is there anything you need
oh i know you you're futaro's friend
where am i on campus
the hospital trust me i was just as surprised as you are
you haven't been taking care of yourself at all
nino i'm sorry for worrying you
i'll be right back
there's still a lot i have to do for the festival
wait i need to hurry
the drama club is depending on me
yotsuba it's night time
the second day's over already
the girl futaro met
that time six years ago
it was you right
you know
how could i not
he showed me your picture so many times
it drove me crazy
i talked to your sisters over at the pancake stand about it
they told me you got lost that day
and he helped you i think i see why you were usuki's teacher
i just wanted to say i'm glad i met you
have you told futaro you were
please don't tell him
why shouldn't i
because he'll be disappointed
usuki's been working so hard during these six years
and i just obsessed over stupid things
and problems that don't matter
instead of helping out
i've caused people trouble
i don't serve any purpose at all
that's really what you think
i know someone who felt like they were worthless
and that no one needed them
the same as you do
it took a long time
but that person's moving forward with life now
i hope you can learn how to leave your past behind too
oh you're up
please so wasuki
let me get by you
i have some stuff to do
i kind of doubt that
everyone's already gone home
then i'll go door to door and apologize
you don't understand
it's not just the drama club
i promised a lot of people i'd help them today
and then i went and let them down
this is all my fault
i failed again
i won't let you leave
you've been prescribed absolute bed rest
i plan to make sure you get it
sit down and relax
and while you do
i'll catch you up on everything that happened during the festival
it's over for you
so stop right there
wait a sec
that was the captain of the track team
yeah she jumped in there and covered for you
apparently she watched the whole show yesterday
but that costume was tailored to fit my measurements
do you remember these two
they're from the clothing club
don't tell me they had to alter it last minute
it's all my fault
a lot of people stepped up
you get it now
it's not because you did something wrong
they want to be there for you
you help out all the time
don't you
it's okay if you ask for help once in a while
let me handle it
since you've always been there for me
uasuki
i feel so terrible for all the trouble i've caused everyone
so please
can you make sure the last day goes well in my place
yeah leave it to me
futara uasugi
long time to see rena
sorry but i had a long day today
could you come by later
thank you for remembering our promise
even though i couldn't keep up my end of it
forgive me
you don't need to worry about that
are you sure though
doesn't it bother you
i mean
the past doesn't matter as much as the present
so no
i'll stop focusing on our past so much
i'm going to find my own place in this world
so
this is it
talk about an embarrassing dream
must have been everything that happened at the festival
i can't believe i went for it
i hope he doesn't mind
it's the last memory we'll have together
but it's time for me to stop lingering in the past
i think now
i'll finally be able to move on
yeah
i can
this concludes the asahi high school festival
the after party
and all of our scheduled programming
i know you
you've done so much for me mr muto
thanks a lot
look at you
it takes a diligent student to be hitting the books during a festival
thank you
i mean
i'm hoping to get into college and become a teacher
i'm following in my mother's footsteps
oh she was a high school teacher i forgot to say
i know
i was her homeroom teacher back when she was in high school
in fact
you look a lot like she did when she was younger
do you mean that
yes
it's almost uncanny
her admiration for me was part of the reason she pursued a teaching career
and she regretted that decision until the very end
in my life
i've made so many mistakes
if you're planning to be a teacher just emulate her
then i'm against it
by the way
i heard there was a fire at one of the stalls
yeah there was but luckily nobody got hurt
well that's good to hear
i wanted to ask you
did you notice a strange old man at the festival
huh
oh that's right
dad was kind of obsessing over this all day long
he's bald and has a beard
it's gray
and kind of fluffy too
yeah
with the kind of face that would look the same if you turned it upside down
so he was there
why are you asking about him
i should probably tell you this in case something happens
that man is
what can i do for you sir
i have something to confess and i think this may be the time to say it
your mother was a student of mine
we were colleagues for a while
and then
she became my wife
in other words
i'm your biological father
father
yes
i've missed you itsuki
for my work as an instructor i've traveled all over japan
and i've thought about you girls every step of the way
then one day
i happened to see ichika in a commercial
i'd like to make up for lost time
no you're too late
i remember everything that mom told us about you
the moment you heard she was going to have quintuplets
you left her
and that was it
how could you
do you have any idea how she felt
you're no father
i'm sorry
please give me a chance to make things right
even if it's too late
i want to at least do what i can as a parent
well
the truth is we already have a dad
you can be on your way now
do you mean nakano
after your mother passed away
did he really do anything good for you girls
face it itsuki you're wasting time chasing after your mother's ghost
and i can't bear to watch my daughter make the same mistake she did
i know without a doubt that teaching is the wrong career for you
and i think there's a part of you that knows it as well
as a father i can't allow you to go down this path
i love my daughters why else would i be here
it's key
yeah
is she okay
has she been acting differently
i haven't seen her since yesterday so i'm not sure
what happened
your biological father's here
and i think he's been in contact with her
oh no
really
it's key hasn't been around
today's the last day too
i wonder what's wrong
she hasn't left her room for the entire day
i see
hold it
you're going to her place right
take this with you
are you sure
that's just what i like about you fu
always consider it
leave the rest to me okay
please take care of itsuki
what's that
wasuki
i have no idea what i'm doing
is all of this a mistake
don't let what that old geezer said get to you
he was obviously just talking out of his ass
i know what mom would say
itsuki
you shouldn't grow up to be like me
i never wanted that for you
and yet i won't change my mind
i'm still aspiring to become like she was
because it's what i want
is that so awful of me
well one thing's for sure
there's nothing that great about becoming a teacher
not every student has potential you know
in fact you'll learn really quickly that some people are just irreparably stupid
but you have to work with them
so you've got to pretend that's not true
investing in other people is a surefire way to wear out your mind and body
then there are some students who will be rebellious
and you can't run away
you have to dig your heels in and fight
take it from someone who knows it's a real pain in the ass
becoming a teacher is a terrible idea
but that isn't the point
you can't let some stranger control your life
this is your dream
no matter how difficult it is
you're the only one who gets to decide if it's worth it or not
but is becoming a teacher actually my dream
all i want is to be like my mother
at least that's what somebody told me once
chasing a dream to be like her
that's not the same as being like her by chasing a dream
as long as you're living your own life
admiring your mother and aspiring to be more like her
isn't a bad thing
in that case
i want to become a great teacher like my mother
and i'm going to teach because it's what i want to do
if that's what you're after
then as your tutor there's only one thing for me to do
i'll support you it's key completely
oh suki
then i have the perfect idea
will you help me study
i'd love to
i appreciate it
but before we begin
there's something important that i need to do
excuse me mr muda
hey there
i have to say i wasn't expecting you to come and talk to me
i take it you finally come to your senses and decided to listen to your father
right
her father huh
you're kidding me
it's you
yep
it's been a long time teach
honestly i would have been fine with never seeing you again
hello there muda
how have you been
nakano
i'm happy i have a chance to apologize to you
after all i left you with a terrible burden
and i'm sorry
no
actually i'm grateful to you
if it wasn't for you and your self-serving behavior my five daughters and i would have never been brought together
is that so
because from where i'm standing it doesn't look like you've kept up with all your responsibilities either
which is why when poor little itski needed her father's help
she couldn't depend on you
so she came to see me
itski's here as well
what are you talking about
look carefully
and you'll see this isn't itski
i've been over here the whole time
what are you girls doing
i deceived you
i'm sorry
but i had to confirm what i already knew would happen
it's just a mistake
what point are you trying to prove here
if you really loved us then you could tell us apart
that's what our mom said
when will you stop bringing up your mother and her absurd ideas
there's nothing good that will come of you trying to emulate a delusional woman
if you really want to follow in her footsteps
don't you think she'd rather you let this go
don't fixate on such silly things
she used to tell us about the choices in life that she regretted
that's right
she made a lot of mistakes
we both know she wouldn't want her daughter to do the same
sorry but you're wrong about that
one thing i know is
even if she felt like she did everything wrong
i would still disagree with her
and that's my right
because my mom and i are different
she gave her all for us
anyone could see how deeply she cared
she was so kind
and there's no way it could be a mistake for a person to live their life like that
what would a child like you know about living
you're the one who's raving and shouting about something you don't understand
you didn't see the hope and faith she had in her children
after all how could you
you weren't there
in fact you have no right to speak of her at all
dad's never
mr. muto
you walked out on mom
and you never even bothered apologizing to her
you're not getting my forgiveness either
i won't let you use me to ease your guilt
you'll be haunted by what you did to her for the rest of your life
how dare you say that
this is pathetic old man
get lost
so did that take care of everything
let me guess you were watching us from afar weren't you
maybe
i'm really grateful to you uesugi
ever since mom passed away
i've been trying to become her
hoping to fill the void that she left behind
at some point
the line between my identity and hers started to blur
before long the faith i used to have in my dreams was wavering
but now i know i don't have to forget my mom
you're the one who taught me that you know
thanks uesugi
i just noticed the sunset really early today huh
guess winter's on its way
what's with you
did i say something funny
you're being so creepy
it's a personal thing
sorry
well anyway
i'm a lot more confident these days and i owe that to you
mom and i are different people
that's obvious but i couldn't see it
not till you showed me
my image of the perfect teacher is still my mother but
but what
i mean
what to say
the point is
that i think of you as perfect too
and i just wanted you to know that
and now
the winner for the best selling shop is
we did it
did everything go okay
did you tell futaro what you wanted to tell him
yeah
and i thanked him for that thing with her father
i meant to thank you all for that too
don't worry about it
it wouldn't be right if we didn't help with a family situation
true but still
i'm glad you did
so thanks okay
you really had to make this awkward didn't you
seriously
you helped a lot
and miku
thank you for posing as me
anytime
besides
i need more chances to perfect my performance
this is about to become a weird obsession for you
i can feel it
it was more than enough to fool someone who doesn't know us
even though we're pretty different
our faces are still the same
yep
i wonder if we'll always be the matching set we are now
but you know what
there's lots of time before we meet up with futaro
let's forget all that and enjoy the after party
guys
how long are we gonna sit here wasting the day away
why don't we go get some food from the stalls huh
all right the stalls
forgot about them
i guess i haven't eaten in a while
and there was a shop that i didn't see yet
but after we do that i gotta go
i'm supposed to meet up with somebody
oh i get it
that's right i saw the nakano sisters earlier
i know ichiko was there
it might have been all five of them
that's onnaida
i'm surprised you knew which one was ichiko right away
yeah i did
this is gonna sound weird
but i can always tell ichiko apart from the rest of the girls
and you can identify all five can't you uesugi
uh
huh
now that you mention it i'm not really sure
first it was nearly impossible
i'm not good at remembering faces to start with
the worst part is they constantly take advantage of that fact
you have no idea how many times they pulled one over on me
they'll be a pain until the bitter end
yeah it sucks to be you
i have a question by the way
which one of the girls was the first one you were able to tell apart flawlessly
hey how about those stalls
not so fast
i want to hear the answer
why are you torturing the poor guy takeda
because i think uesugi might be keeping a little secret from us
there's nothing to tell you
then why are you in such a rush to get away
friends aren't supposed to keep secrets you know
forget it no comment all right
i know what it is
you like one of them don't you
a student's job is to study
for years i felt like that was all that mattered
but no there's no reason to cut everything else out of my life
studying friendship work fun relationships
those girls do everything to the fullest
i was so stuck in my ways until they came along and taught me how to live
i just wish i hadn't kept them waiting for so long while i was getting it through my head
if they hadn't changed me for the better i would probably still be alone to this day
but what's the point of shopping around if you didn't bring money with you
the resting area is a total lifesaver huh
yeah
why wouldn't i i want to enjoy the festival until the very end
okay it's almost time now
oh sookie when today's events are over
we'll each be waiting for you in our rooms
with our own thoughts and feelings
hoping that you'll show up
but sadly you'll have to choose only one of those rooms to visit
we realize that this idea is going to cause a lot of heartache for you and for us
but this is what we've decided to do
we sincerely hope you understand
iwasuki
this concludes the asahi high school festival
the after party
and all of our scheduled programming
so you've made your choice
you figured it out
good job frutero
it's over now
when we talked that night
you had already decided
this is just the start
wasuki
there it is
hey
took me a while huh
what's going on what are you doing here
I came to see you. What else?
Really? You're kidding, right?
No, it can't be. No way this is happening.
I get it. I'm surprised I did this, too.
Also, did you have to make me wait so long?
Why weren't you in your room?
Because I was positive you'd go to someone else instead.
These were fresh when I bought them, you know.
Hey, is that...
You gave me the coupon, remember?
Here, have some.
You waited here for a long time.
Well, yeah, because I was hoping we could eat these together.
So, anyway, I, uh...
I need to make sure we're both on the same page now that you know how I feel.
Do you want to...
Sorry, but no!
No!
Hello?
Uasuki?
Uh, is anybody in there?
I worked up a lot of courage to come here.
Wasn't expecting such a quick answer.
Listen, I'm really honored you chose me and everything, so I hope you don't take this the wrong way.
I don't think you should settle for someone like me, Uasuki.
I guarantee you there are plenty of girls who'd be better for you.
Why would you say that?
Well, I mean, look at my sisters.
Any one of them would...
Stop, Yotsuba.
I'm not asking any of your sisters.
I'm here to find out how you feel.
Come back!
She got away.
Uasuki.
Itsuki, where is everyone?
Run, that way.
That's where Yotsuba went.
You don't need to know anything else right now, okay?
Worrying about us four will only cause more pain.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry.
There was something you always used to say, Yotsuba.
In fact, you said it so much that it got annoying.
Let's make sure we don't leave camp with any regrets.
So this time, let's make sure we all walk away without any regrets, okay?
I want to make sure we finish the festival without any regrets.
I'm not giving up now!
Get back here!
I'm so sorry, Uasuki.
But I've accepted that I can't be special.
Because I don't deserve to be.
You guys!
Where'd you go?
Ow!
Oh no, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I should have been paying attention.
It was my fault.
Uh-oh, it's getting really late.
Yeah, I guess we should take the bus home, huh?
Huh?
Hmm?
I can't.
I'm all out of money after buying that good luck charm earlier.
Are you stupid?
I only have 200 yen on me, and that's not enough for the both of us.
Guess you're stuck here.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Have a good night, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Look at that, it's gone.
My family's real poor, so I only get 5 yen for allowance.
That's lame, huh?
Aren't you sad that you don't have very much money, Futuro?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
That's how my family is, too.
My mom has to work really hard all by herself so she can take care of us.
To be honest, sometimes I feel like...
Maybe life would be a little bit better for my mom if I wasn't around, you know?
That's not true.
So I decided I'm going to study as hard as I can, and I'll become really smart.
Then one day I can get a job where I'll earn lots of money.
That'll make everything easier for her.
If I do that, then there'll finally be a reason for me to be here.
Wow, cool.
You're like a real grown-up.
All right.
I'm gonna study hard like you are.
If I get smarter, I bet I can find a great job.
And then I'll be super rich and things will be better for my little sister.
Maybe that's the way you make yourself important.
Let's do it.
Together.
I'll try my best for my mom's sake.
And you can do it to help your little sister.
We'll study like crazy.
Yeah.
Hey.
Why don't we make it official with a wish?
For a hundred yen a piece?
Yotsuba.
That ribbon.
It looks good on you.
Thanks a lot, Mom.
Maybe now people can tell me apart from my sisters.
Well, that's doubtful.
What you wear doesn't make much difference.
There's more to you than that.
It's not just the ribbon.
I study a lot more than they do.
And I got first place the other day, too.
See, Mom, I'm winning.
I'm so far ahead of everyone else in every way.
I'm not the same anymore.
Mom, look at these.
Do you like them?
Yes, they're very cute.
I changed my hair just like Yotsuba did.
Yotsuba, it's wonderful that you're giving your all.
Working hard is a good thing.
But, dear, you don't have to compete.
Each one of you is special in your own unique way.
As your mother, I want you girls to stay close the rest of your lives.
But you should always remember one thing.
What matters is that the five of you are together.
Wherever you may be.
I always believed she was going to get better, but she never did.
Pardon me, children.
I suppose we've never been particularly close.
But from now on, I'm going to be the one looking after you.
Mom, we just started middle school this year.
But there's no way the five of us can stick together the way we used to.
We may look alike, but we can't be the same anymore.
Hey, Dad, guess what?
Look at my test score.
I did the best out of all five of us.
That's wonderful.
Oh, and the track team asked me to join, but I turned them down.
After all, I gotta be responsible and put my studies first, right?
Of course. Keep up the good work.
He was kind of cold, huh?
Mom would have praised me a lot more than that.
She would have praised me, right?
I wonder if Futuro's still studying this late at night.
You sure you don't need this anymore, Yotsuba?
Nah, I need to focus on school anyways.
Okay, then maybe I'll borrow it.
Awesome, it's improving a little every time.
I just have to keep on pushing.
Hey, Yotsuba.
My history grade, it's gotten way better.
It's because of that game you lent me.
Wow.
Really?
That's great, Miku.
I need to work harder.
I'll study all I can.
Then I'll become really smart.
That way, I can work for a company that pays me lots.
I still failed.
What's the point of studying, then?
You don't need to be special.
What's important is that the five of you remain together.
Why does it matter if we're all together?
I don't understand what you mean.
I don't need to be special.
I'm selected to run in the interscholastic meet.
Well done.
Are you watching, Mom?
Mom.
The whole room is praising me.
There's a lot of people who need me, and it's because I'm me, not because I'm one of the
Nakano sisters.
You've been training really hard recently.
Listen, how are your grades?
I can always help you with your homework if you want me to.
I'm different from the rest of you now.
I'm not like you.
That's right.
I'm the best of the sisters.
I'm special.
You've had two make-up exams now, and you've failed both of them, which means you'll repeat
your grade.
Is that true?
No way.
You're joking.
No.
This isn't a joke.
But ma'am, I've been doing so well in my club, and on the basketball team.
None of those things matter.
I gave you plenty of warning, Miss Nakano, and yet you continued trying to join every club
that you could find.
Gather your belongings.
Thanks.
A transfer?
Luckily, I have a contact who's on the executive board at a coeducational school.
I'll send you there when summer break is over while your sisters remain here.
Wait.
Wait, so just me?
I don't understand.
I thought I was special.
I worked so hard to make sure I had a purpose in this world.
After all that, how could I end up alone?
What am I going to do if the others aren't there with me?
How do I become someone special?
I don't know where I'm supposed to go from here.
Wait.
If Yotsuba has to transfer, then all of us are transferring.
You're being ridiculous!
Didn't the rest of you girls pass your exams?
I passed mine with no trouble.
But that was only because I cheated.
What?
Please tell me that's not true.
Aww.
We all did, actually.
You guys...
Stop it!
Why would you do this for me?
Yotsuba, I don't know what's going on in that thick skull of yours,
but you're crazy if you think we're going to let you be apart from us!
We'll all stick together wherever we are.
Remember, that's what Mom taught us to do.
Yotsuba, we'll be fine.
I mean, we're all one-fifth of each other, right?
So, together, the five of us can get through anything.
I guess this is what Mom meant when she told me all that stuff.
I'm going to stop caring about which one of us is the best.
From now on, I'll live for my sisters.
My sisters.
A perfect score?
My sisters are the only reason I have anything good.
My memories.
My feelings.
I have to forget them.
You're not hurt, are you?
All of your sisters are good people, Yotsuba.
They're amazing.
I love each one of them.
I'm really honored that I was able to tutor you guys.
But still, if you weren't involved, I would have given up a while ago.
Why would you say something like that?
I'm a weak human being, and I'll keep tripping up for the rest of my life.
I know this is rich coming from a loser like me.
But for all my future screw-ups, I'd be happy if I had you by my side.
You give me peace.
Because you're my anchor, Yotsuba.
And I would love to be that for you.
So if you hate me, then that's fine.
But please just tell me how you feel.
Oh, Asuki, I...
Tell him.
Let's put an end to all of this.
The truth is, I hate you.
I hate you.
I love you.
I do.
I tried, Asuki, but I can't lie to you.
I've always loved you.
I'm sorry about this.
But there's something I still need to do.
What?
You're not dating?
I guess not.
Interesting.
You guys aren't together.
Which means it's not over yet.
Futaro technically still doesn't belong to anyone.
Come on!
Get it together!
Yotsuba said she loves you, remember?
So it's mutual.
Make a move or she'll start to resent you.
You're right.
Thanks, Ichika.
That helps.
Even if you were the one he ended up choosing, I would still be happy for you.
I didn't understand Nino then, but I get it now.
You knew I liked Fu long before what happened yesterday.
You've known how I felt about him from the beginning.
That's why I don't want you to be worried about me anymore.
Nino, you're my sister.
How can I not be worried about you?
Alright, fine.
Then I guess things are over between us.
If this is how you insist it has to be,
then from now on, you're not my sister.
Yotsuba.
Huh?
You should go inside soon or you're going to catch a cold.
Miku.
Yotsuba, actually.
My name is Yotsuba.
What's this about?
I was thinking,
if Futuro didn't choose me,
then I would become you.
So I could be with him instead.
What do you think?
I don't think that's right.
It just isn't.
It's cold.
Do you want to go talk somewhere else?
Wow.
Karaoke with only the two of us.
This is a first, huh?
Yotsuba?
Yeah?
What's up?
It was a joke.
I didn't mean all that stuff I said about trying to become you.
Obviously, I can pretend I'm you,
but I can't be you.
For one thing, this juice is way too sweet for me.
Look.
I'm still mad at you, though.
Because I would never do anything to hurt Futuro the way you are right now.
I can tell you're having a hard time figuring out what you want.
If you like him so much, why is it such a difficult decision to make?
It isn't that.
I've had these feelings for Uasuki for a really long time.
And they haven't changed, not even a little bit.
That makes even less sense.
You have no good reason to hesitate.
Unless you're still hung up on what happened back at our other school.
You should stop worrying about all of us.
Go out with him.
Did that sound like I meant it?
I figured it would turn out this way.
But still, I can't deny that it hurts me.
It's just hard to keep my feelings in check.
Because I care so much.
So, if we accept how you feel, then you should do the same for us.
This isn't easy.
I should have been more careful.
I didn't consider what Nino was going through.
No wonder she's angry at me.
Nino told me once that in love, we may not be allies, but we're not enemies either.
Yeah.
Okay, now that we both agree on that, I'll battle you my way.
And my strategy is simply not to encourage you.
We might as well sing.
Sounds fun.
Get ready.
Cause I'm gonna sing a whole lot better than you.
That's what you think.
Hey, look!
The weather's so nice!
I know it was my idea to sing, but I didn't expect to be here for the whole night.
Hey, Miku.
Let's go home.
To our sisters.
Yotsuba's mistaken about one thing.
Then again, I'm probably never going to tell her what I really think.
If my sisters and I had never transferred to this school,
then Futura wouldn't have walked into our lives.
When you look at it that way, it's hard to see it as a negative.
It's because I met him.
That I...
We should go.
I couldn't become Yotsuba.
But the truth is, Yotsuba could never be me either.
I couldn't wrap my head around that at first.
But now, I finally like myself enough to believe it.
Itsuki.
You got a minute?
Um, sure, what is it?
There's something I want to talk about.
Somewhere more private?
More private?
Okay then.
In here.
So...
What's up, Uesugi?
Here?
Oh no, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Carrie.
I don't understand.
Why am I still so uneasy?
This place looks handy.
You're the one who drove a wedge between the five of us.
You know that, don't you?
What I did was selfish.
I'm sorry for not respecting your feelings.
I was being too pushy.
But still, it doesn't change how I feel about it.
And what I wish for.
Oh, save it.
I know you still expect to be coddled.
I'll never approve of.
Oh, it's just some mice.
Yeah, sure.
Mice.
That was close.
You think it's too risky to go for the door?
I don't know, but could you give me some space?
It's going to look really bad if those two see us like this.
Anyway, lunch break is almost over.
Let's go back.
Hold on!
What?
I gathered up all of my courage to tell you this.
What I want most is for you to approve of me dating Uesugi.
I just told you.
Listen!
It doesn't have to be right now.
It could be months or years.
I don't know how long it'll take you to change your mind.
But eventually, I want you to understand and accept how much I love Uesugi.
My love for him is just as strong as yours.
You're right.
Even if you apologized or tried everything in the world to convince me,
we both know I wouldn't buy it at all.
And yet, in spite of that, you're still dead set on going down such a painful path?
Yes, Nino.
I love him and you guys with all my heart.
And nothing's going to change that.
Honestly, that's stupid.
But it sounds like something you'd say.
There are certain shackles that come with being a quintuplet.
And when I saw you step out of them, I was jealous of you.
After all that we've been through, do you still think of me as someone to compete with?
Of course I do.
We're sisters, which means we'll always be aware of what's going on with each other.
Sometimes as friends.
Sometimes foes.
We're like...
I get it.
Rivals.
Well, this battle isn't over yet.
Because I'll be observing your relationship with him from a distance.
You show even the slightest weakness.
And I'll come to take him away from you.
Right.
That's all I wanted to say.
You can come out now, you little rats.
You knew the whole time?
They can explain.
You were here too?
For how long?
Please don't tell me you heard everything.
Sorry.
I hope you heard what I said, Fu.
I meant every word.
Keep your guard up or it's all over.
Okay.
I'll try to remember that.
You sure got yourself involved with a crazy group of siblings.
But I think I can finally say this now.
You're not alone.
You never will be.
Congratulations, Iwasuki.
Um...
Listen.
I just wanted to say that I appreciate you inviting me out today.
Sorry to steal your day off.
No.
I'm glad.
It'll be fun.
You think so?
I just figured it's kind of hard to find time to be alone during school.
That's true.
Especially since my sisters are always around.
The train has stopped due to obstacles on the track.
We deeply apologize for the...
This seems backwards.
I guess so.
Yeah.
Please, feel free to order as much food as you want.
Everything's on me.
Yay!
Mmm, it's yummy.
I'm glad you like it.
This is embarrassing.
Who goes to a family restaurant on a first date?
I think it's kind of endearing.
Coupons, too?
Is that bad?
It's so tacky to use coupons on a date.
Say what you want, but he's obviously trying his best.
You're hoping for a referral to a sports universe.
University, right?
Uh-huh.
You could do a lot of different things with that.
Is it your dream to become a professional athlete?
No.
To be honest, I don't remember what I wanted to be as a kid.
It's been so long, but one thing I do know is that I'm really in my element when
I'm supporting other people.
It happened because I gave up on something.
But then I realized it was part of myself I could be proud of.
Yeah.
It sounds like you.
I have you to thank.
You're the reason I figured that out.
What?
Really?
Of course.
Uh...
Anyway, if I do get into university somewhere, then that's probably the kind of career I
want to aim for.
Uh, sounds good.
Mm-hmm.
It's so frustrating.
We should go now.
Contain yourself, Nino.
I'm sorry.
The library's not very exciting, is it?
It was.
Anything's fun for me as long as we can do it together, Iwasuki.
Okay.
Then do you mind if I take you to one more place?
Let's go!
Look at her.
She doesn't even need encouragement from us, does she?
It's the playground.
Takes you back, huh?
Remember?
You like this rusty old swing.
I did.
But I thought you were supposed to be taking me to visit your favorite places today.
Right.
The restaurant my parents took me to, and the library where I study.
But I thought you were supposed to be taking me to visit your favorite places today.
Right.
The restaurant my parents took me to, and the library where I study.
Since the day you brought me here, this place is special too.
Hmm. You sure about this? I'm kind of hesitating a bit.
Being happy apart from my sisters? I don't know.
It kind of feels like something that I'm not allowed to do.
How do I know if I'm making the right decision?
Yotsuba, remember how far you jumped from here? Can you do it again?
Um, sure. Sit back and watch a pro!
How was that?
Yotsuba, if I can make it as far as you just did, I want to ask you a question.
What are you...?
Here goes!
Hey, be careful! You might get hurt!
Watch me!
Come on! I know I can do this!
Don't die!
Yotsuba...
Right now...
I'm not even mature enough to put together a proper date.
But I'm gonna do my best to become a better man.
So I can stand proud next to you someday.
Whether we're on the right path or not...
We'll walk it together.
So please...
If you'll have me, I want to be by your side for the rest of my life.
I love you.
Will you marry me?
Don't scare me like that!
I thought...
I mean...
You're skipping so many steps!
Oh!
I guess I am.
I'm sorry.
People can get creeped out if you say that too early, you know?
And by people, I mean other people!
I understand.
Do you mind if I start over?
Yotsuba?
The thing I wanted to be...
I remember it now.
It was something a lot of little girls dreamed of being.
A bride.
So, Iwasugi.
You have to promise...
That one day...
You'll make my dream come true for real.
...
Hey, this is difficult for me.
But there's something really important I need to confess to all of you.
I didn't want to tell you, but...
My university?
Um, it's in Tokyo!
Huh?
I mean, I kind of figured it was.
Yeah, that's why we didn't bother asking you.
Obviously, you'd go to school in a big city.
That's right.
But don't worry, it doesn't bother us at all.
Oh!
Cool.
Good luck on your exams.
It's not like we can't come visit you.
True.
Thanks, guys.
I'm very happy I met all of you.
Later.
Kay!
I'll see you soon!
Just as we expected, huh?
Yeah, he actually looks sad for once.
You're right.
That kind of makes me happy.
To tell the truth.
Knowing I could see that look on his face.
I'm lucky.
Tommy, you promised me you wouldn't cry.
So did you, though.
Train's this, goal's that, I don't know if I can ever be like the rest of you.
You'll be okay, Nino.
We'll figure it out.
Well, if it's for you, I can stick around here a bit longer.
around here a bit longer.
That'd be nice.
Thanks a lot.
It's been so long!
Hey, Nakano, we're ready for you.
I'll be right over.
I made the cut.
College.
I did it more.
Hey, Yotsuba.
Are you sure you'll be okay living alone in college?
I figured you would be scared.
You're always worrying about us, Ichika.
We'll do just fine living apart.
I mean, no matter how far we are.
I bet you've never been this nervous in your life.
No, I haven't.
But I know that I'm not alone.
And, of course, neither are they.
I'm not alone.
Ichika just said she's almost here.
Oh, good.
It's probably about time for us to get ready, too, then.
We haven't all been together in so long.
This place never changes, does it?
I'm home now, Japan.
You miss me?
Come on, it was just a vacation.
Oh, wow.
Hey, Itsuki.
Thanks for picking me up.
I forgot you're a celebrity, though.
Gotta be discreet.
Welcome in.
Oh.
Never mind, it's just you.
Ichika, long time no see.
It's good to see both of you are doing okay.
I mean, look, you've got so many customers in here.
Ha ha.
You sure mastered the art of sarcasm while you were in the States.
So what was it like for you spending all that time in America?
I don't think I'm doing so good with my English grammar.
Ichika, it's doing so well.
Oh, right.
You're particular.
Well, I am a teacher, after all.
Are you gonna stay and eat?
We'll make something for you.
Awesome.
Hope you can stomach our food now that you've been spoiled by American cafes.
Cafes?
When did I talk to you about cafes?
You didn't, but Nino's constantly stalking your Insta.
Stop, Miku!
Don't throw me under the bus!
How about this?
I'll share your place on social, too, so more people can find it.
No, don't.
If we used your following to gain business, it'd be more than we can even handle.
While I appreciate the thought, I think we'd better wait on it.
We've been getting more and more regular customers recently,
so I want to see how much we can grow without anyone helping.
Besides Futuro's dad.
When he lent us the place, it already had practically everything we needed.
What's wrong?
Oh, you're so adorable!
I just want to show you off even more now!
Well, if you're acting career tanks, I guess I could let you work here.
She's a little less adorable, but she's cute in her own way.
Finally, here comes the moment of the hour!
Hey, I'm so happy Elif you could make it!
Why are you covered in sweat?
I was too excited and couldn't stay still, so I decided I might as well bike all the way over!
What?!
But that's so far!
Why would you do that right before your wedding ceremony?
I hope Uesugi's taking the train at least.
Yeah, he actually got into town yesterday.
He's probably taking a nap right now.
What?
Looks like we finally have to accept reality.
Right.
That's why we planned this top secret early morning meeting.
Oh yeah, my makeup artist is planning to be there too, by the way.
We're really doing this?
You're not allowed to chicken out now.
You were into it at the beginning.
That's right!
And I'm pretty sure Uesugi won't have a problem with it.
Ichika, we're all set!
I'm wearing mine!
This is your wedding gift from all of us.
The earrings that Mom used to wear.
Yotsuba, we'll do it as soon as you're ready.
Okay, I can handle the pain!
Stay strong.
It's just gonna be one quick jab.
Here we go!
Congratulations on your wedding, Yotsuba!
Yotsuba!
Thank you.
walid
Dong
Thank you!
Pardon me.
you know that the bride's family is here thank goodness i thought he wasn't going to show up
why didn't you come to the rehearsal my apologies i had decided not to come but then i changed my
mind at the last minute father what a surprise there really isn't any reason for you to call
me that you know i'm sorry i'm just so surprised and honored that you're here i know i was
disrespectful of you when i was younger usugi i want you to answer me one thing um okay is my
yotsuba happy from the bottom of her heart yes and so am i i'll have some wine please
oh sure one second let's see which way to the groom's dressing room well it's been over a decade
since my mother passed away it happened right after she finally achieved her dream of opening a restaurant
which meant our family was left with the enormous debt that came with starting the business
as for miku and nino they're doing great with it dad lent it to them to help them but i think he
also did it as a way of keeping mom's dream alive i want to get married to the woman i love
and love her until i die just like both of my fathers that's quite enough oh i'm sorry sir
being called father i suppose i'm still not used to it excuse me my apologies for interrupting
but the bride's calling for you uh i uh go on ahead
hey maruo we're getting old now aren't we i'm surprised i thought you only drank on happy occasions
i do which is why i'm drinking so you think it's gonna work out well as parents that's not exactly
our question to answer still i'm sure it's not going to be easy after all he did choose to marry one of my
daughters
hi futaro your favorite game the final one if you love the bride you can pick her out
before i go on i just wanted to personally thank everyone for taking the time to come to our
reception it means a lot to both of us that you're joining our celebration today the quintuplet game
you're inside this is a sacred event none of you should be wearing a wedding dress except yotsuba
you did this for shits and giggles look i know it's a little bit off the wall but i think it was a great
idea and besides it isn't just for fun the bride's family is supposed to be protective right i mean
i say that but i'm the real bride so don't ask me don't listen to her i'm the bride obviously i'm
yotsuba you can tell the difference i know you can you're all such morons i thought you might be at
least a little more mature by now i guess it's good to see you have it changed but i'm not fooled
you i'd like to thank my family once again i am where i am today because of my father and
my mother and of course my four wonderful sisters i'm glad the man i call father came into my life
when he did you're clearly each guy first of all there's our oldest sister each guy who's always
around to keep us together when times are tough and as most of you know she's a very successful
actress i hope she knows how much i look up to her thank goodness you really worried your big sis
how nostalgic you used to give me such a hard time back then the public only sees that cool beauty
persona but i know that you're sloppy slow and lazy that's the truth not sure what i did to deserve
that even so you stayed strong no matter what that was beautiful to me you're an incredible big sister
i see through you too nino my second sister nino is the most hot-tempered but she's tough disciplined
and knows just what to say to encourage someone and she's so elegant there are a lot of things i can
learn from her all right nice going you got me proud of yourself
why did you point me out you just have to find yotsuba some people might see your strictness as a
character flaw but really it's your strength you can be harsh on the people you love sometimes but you
do it because you truly care for a long time i didn't know how i should respond to that i'm sorry
it's fine because i don't regret it one bit that's good
miku right yeah miku's older than me but strangely she doesn't always seem like she is
it's more like we're friends who found ourselves in the same situation
as a friend and a sister i'm doubly proud of her for achieving her dream
i get scared sometimes am i handling things okay you don't need me to answer that you've always been
the type to be at war with your own mind and you've won so many times look at the things you've
accomplished so believe in yourself you're more capable than you know
i kind of figured that was what you'd say oh futuro thank you
and last but not least itsuki
you got it wrong on yotsuba
just kidding
yup i'm itsuki wow i'm getting so good at this
and itsuki is particularly special because she's the only one i can call little sister
but despite being younger she's way more put together than i am i was confused and
lost at one point in life and itsuki was there to give me a nudge forward
damn it you had me so freaked out let me give you a piece of my mind none of this would have
happened without you once i met you everything changed you and that stupid curry ruined my life
that day me really before you came around i didn't think it was possible for someone to be so
insensitive and rude and then you accidentally kissed me what that was i don't think i'll ever be able
to get along with a jerk like you look at that she's come back to her high school self you can't
blame her i'm just saying you get under your skin you've got a lot of nerve calling me careless
and you're my bride my yotsuba
yes you got it right
if not for my amazing sisters everything that's happened in my life would have been completely
different there were times when being a quintuplet felt like a drawback but i have hundreds no thousands
of wonderful memories because of them
at this point i know this family better than i ever wanted to i may have been your tutor but you
guys taught me a lot of lessons yourselves and as annoying as it is to say this out loud i'm really
proud to know each one of you whenever i think about how fortunate i am to call the four of you my sisters
it still floors me our family's unconventional and sometimes we might come across as a little weird
but i'll always love it exactly the way it is
oh five years and finally we get a moment to relax now that all the adrenaline's gone away i'm
suddenly super exhausted and you tried to pretend like you weren't nervous in there
not as nervous as you though during the big kiss your hands were totally trembling
capital anybody would have been jittery people were watching and besides i was thinking of that time
five years ago
pretty sure that was excuse me but it seems you forgot something back in the bridal suite
oh yeah thanks a lot
on second thought i won't be needing it anymore
you can just throw it away
as you wish ma'am
are you sure that ribbon's your trademark
it's okay
each one of you is special in your own unique way
i may be a quintuplet but now i have somebody who can always pick me out
what are you guys up to great ceremony nice going newlyweds what does it look like we're up to
what's supposed to come right after a wedding the honeymoon trip wait a sec don't tell me all of
you are coming we sure are we just need to settle on where to go what have i married into
it'll be even more fun if everyone's with us right obviously let's do the thing where we point
to what we like if the bride's okay with it so am i i seem to remember us having a fight over this
once oh yeah in high school here we go one two
rise and shine uosuke
hope you slept okay you seemed so peaceful that it kind of made me want to go to sleep too
don't catch a cold can you stop lazing around on our couch and get up now
but our wedding day
um sorry slow down there tiger come on no time for daydreaming we need to make a decision
about what it was your idea we're picking a spot for our graduation trip
all right i did think that hey each sister points to the place that she wants i don't get a say we all
know how it's gonna go and yet you still don't think it's a bad idea here we go fingers down on the
count of three hey hold on one two i want to see ryoma sakamoto but we did history stuff on the
school trip let's go to okinawa there's a lot of good food in hokkaido though why not there
wow we gotta pick somewhere that's pretty for sightseeing hey i know rock paper scissors time
oh yeah i had the same thought back then too
oh you're all over
oh
quintuplets really are a pain
iğı
oh
Thank you.
Oh
Thank you!